THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
It feels so strange
now that it's time to leave.
Corporal Joo Sang-uk,
you have to keep in touch.
It's not like I'm going far.
We'll probably run into each other.
And you better not ignore me,
treating me like some old man.
An old man?
- Barracks 1, at ease!
- Salute!
Yes, I got it. Is all your stuff packed?
- Yes, we're all set.
- Yes, sir.
- The transport's here, so let's go.
I wonder if Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun
and Seong-jae are doing okay.
I'm not sure about Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun
but I'm sure Seong-jae is doing just fine.
Right? He'll do great.
- Let's go.
BARRACKS 1, KANG SEONG-JAE
BARRACKS 1
A HEARTY MEAL IS THE START OF CAMARADERIE
FOOD WASTE TRAFFIC LIGHT
And Ganglim Outpost,
4th Company, 1st Battalion is
tied for first place! Congratulations!
- My goodness.
- What?
- We won! We did it!
- Yes!
We did it!
GANGLIM OUTPOST SHUTDOWN
So why isn't the Quest complete?
It was an incredibly difficult decision.
Both teams presented wonderful dishes
and while the Officers' Mess's score
was slightly higher
because it was more suitable
for military meals
the Ganglim Outpost received bonus points
resulting in a tie between the two teams.
So, after a discussion among the judges
we've decided to hold
a final one-on-one showdown
to determine the ultimate winner.
Hero.
You have failed to complete the Quest.
All skills and recipes will disappear.
The Chef's Path will now end.
Since it's a tie for first place
it looks like we'll have one more round.
But hey, what does it matter? Who are we?
- We're Ganglim, aren't we?
- Ganglim Outpost!
Let's take this all the way
and win the whole thing!
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- You're not hurt, right?
- No.
All right, this competition isn't
a team battle. It's an individual one.
A one-on-one showdown.
What?
One representative soldier from each team
- will have 50 minutes to complete a dish.
- A representative?
Seong-jae, get ready. You got this!
Let's make sure we win this time.
- Representatives.
- Show them what you got.
Please step forward!
Come on, walk tall. Go!
FINAL EPISODE
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
That was a dramatic tie.
How are you feeling right now?
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae?
Hey, what's with him?
I know. He suddenly zoned out.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
- How are you feeling right now?
Well...
The thing is...
I think I need to think a little more
about what would be good to make.
Oh, okay. I understand.
- Corporal Lee Ho-yeong.
Did you anticipate a rematch?
I made a few small mistakes
so I don't think
I was able to perform at 100%.
I'll focus more on the individual match
and ensure that I come out the winner.
It seems the defending champion
is left with some regrets, as expected.
Okay, then, we will now announce
the mission for the tiebreaker.
This mission
is to develop a new special meal.
This time, with no budget limit,
you are to create one special meal.
My mouth is already watering
thinking about what dishes we'll see.
We'll take a short break to get set up
then we'll start
the competition right away.
Every day, as I'd follow the status window
complete Quests, gain Experience Points
and level up.
For the first time, I felt certain
I could actually accomplish something.
Stir-fry the beef with sesame oil.
Use vinegar to eliminate the odor
from the old rice.
Add water to lower the salinity.
Add Cheongyang chili peppers
for some kick.
When using the Rose-Knife item
your cooking grade increases
by half a star.
Perfectly grilled pork belly. Three stars.
What can I do without my status window?
Whether it's cooking
or standing guard at the Outpost...
Right now, I can't do anything.
Seong-jae, are you okay?
What's with you all of a sudden?
- It's nothing.
- Come on.
Hey. Tying for first is
a huge accomplishment.
We gave it our all, right?
But...
- I feel it's all meaningless now.
- Hey, Kang Seong-jae.
What, you think it's all over?
It's not over.
- Just start over, that's all.
- He's right.
Let's plan the menu again.
Since it's a special meal
what about something
like ginseng chicken soup?
That sounds great.
What about grilled eel over rice?
We could really bring out
that smoky flavor.
Smoky sounds good. Hey, what about
that smoky-flavored chicken
you made before?
Kang Seong-jae.
You got anything you want to make?
Just...
- I just want to do well.
- What?
You're already doing great.
What? All of a sudden...
What's gotten into you?
In just a moment, we'll begin
the second round
to decide our winning team.
We ask all participating teams to please
make your way to the event area.
Seong-jae.
Don't get hung up on the results.
For this last one, without any regrets
I hope you'll make the dish
you really want to make.
And just trust yourself. You'll be fine.
We have a wide variety of ingredients
prepared for you here.
Choose from the ingredients we have here
and create your own special meal.
We will now begin
the final one-on-one showdown.
- Hey, Kang Seong-jae, let's go!
- Hey, Seong-jae, we're here with you!
My mind is a complete blank.
I have no idea what I should cook.
Can I even cook without the status window?
29TH DIVISION COOKING COMPETITION
Is he going to stare
at the ingredients all day?
Time's really flying by.
It looks like Corporal Lee Ho-yeong
is already set to start cooking.
- Grade A onion from Muan.
- Glossy surface, substantial weight.
And that pungent aroma
that hits your nose.
These are the things I perceived
with my own senses every day.
Even though the status window is gone
I might've known it all along.
A fresh, sweet smell,
just the right firmness
and golden skin.
This is it.
If you press it firmly like this...
See how it springs right back up?
This is the sign of fresh meat.
- Grade S domestic pork.
- Put your nose right up to it.
And give it a good sniff.
You'll smell a savory, nutty aroma,
not a gamey one.
DOMESTIC GRADE C EGGS
Domestic Grade C eggs.
- What are you doing?
- Oh, gosh.
The eggs seemed a bit off,
so I was shaking one.
I think I can hear it sloshing.
What I need isn't some amazing recipe.
What dish do I want to eat most right now?
The knife I've held every day
feels unfamiliar.
It feels unusually heavy,
and the blade feels dull.
This is so different from
just a few minutes ago.
What is he doing?
There are no guidelines.
No dotted lines or angle markers.
I can't see any of them.
Corporal Lee Ho-yeong's
knife skills are savage.
Just look at that speed! He's so fast.
And precise.
Corporal Lee Ho-yeong.
You can afford to take it easy.
You could probably win
with just your left hand.
Kang Seong-jae! Don't worry!
Just do what you always do.
- Cooking is all about heart! Heart!
- It's not even a match.
- Go, Ganglim.
- Go!
Just like I always do.
Stay calm.
- Kang Seong-jae's luck is running out.
- Right.
So now even you won't help me.
A HEARTY MEAL IS THE START OF CAMARADERIE
You have completed the daily quest.
Your knife skill proficiency
has increased.
All the countless cuts
I've made until now.
I have to remember the feeling
from those times.
Let's go!
All right, 30 minutes left.
He's doing pretty well,
even though that's not his usual knife.
Only bad cooks blame their gear.
Like me. You got this!
- 30 minutes is plenty of time.
- Totally.
I made rice every day
but now I hesitate
over every little thing.
To make delicious rice
is the most difficult thing of all.
I'm only just now realizing that.
Dad.
Seong-jae, do you know
why rice is so important?
No.
It's because rice brings
all the side dishes together.
No matter how good the side dishes are,
they feel incomplete without rice.
You shouldn't wash the rice so roughly.
You'll hurt it.
Like this.
Gently now.
Let it slip through your fingers.
Like this.
Now you try.
Yes, maybe even before
the status window showed up
Dad had already taught me everything.
That's it.
Kang Seong-jae is starting
to pick up the pace.
It looks like he's finally
found his rhythm.
I wonder what special dish
he'll come up with.
- What's he trying to do?
- I have no idea.
The exact measurements and ratios
for the seasoning don't matter.
What really matters is
how it tastes to me.
Now that the status window is gone
the only one I can truly rely on
is myself.
I need a deep, rich umami flavor.
The air is already filling up
with a delicious aroma.
And we're all very curious to see
what kind of dish
Lee Ho-yeong will create.
That rich, buttery aroma
is making my mouth water.
Kang Seong-jae's dish, on the other hand
has a somewhat familiar feel to it.
It doesn't quite look like a special meal
so I have to admit,
I'm a little concerned.
With two dishes that are
so completely different
we'll see how they turn out.
All eyes are on them now.
All right, 20 minutes left.
- 20 minutes is plenty of time.
- More than enough.
All right, ten minutes left.
Both contestants need to start
wrapping things up.
Five minutes remaining.
He has to wrap it up now.
With soy sauce and balsamic vinegar
he was able to make it
look just like caviar.
- That's amazing.
- Yes.
One minute remaining.
All right, time's up.
Please stop what you're doing.
Let's give a big round of applause
to our two soldiers
for all their hard work.
Seong-jae.
You get cut by knives and burned by fire.
You've got to wear those scars
to be a real chef.
Got it?
My goodness, did he really make this
in just 50 minutes?
I saw it with my own two eyes,
and I still can't believe it.
It looks like
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae
misunderstood the theme this time.
It's a far cry from the elegance
of French cuisine.
Yes.
- The reactions are good.
- Excellent.
It's going to be fine.
Corporal Lee Ho-yeong,
would you please introduce your dish?
Corporal Lee Ho-yeong!
Vol-au-vent is French
for "flight in the wind,"
meaning it's incredibly light.
Inside the puff pastry
I've placed a filling
of cream sauce and chicken.
All right, first, you will taste
the dish from Corporal Lee Ho-yeong
of the Officers' Mess.
This creation
was made with a precise technique
to make the outside crispy
while keeping the inside perfectly moist.
It feels like...
- Looking at...
- A piece of art.
Next, I've prepared a truffle risotto.
I enhanced the aroma
with truffle mushrooms and oil.
It's an explosion of different flavors
in my mouth.
This risotto has a subtle truffle aroma
and it's cooked perfectly al dente.
It almost feels like I'm dining
in a high-end restaurant.
For dessert,
I've prepared a sweet creme brulee.
Please, enjoy.
It's not too sweet. I like that.
A meal this luxurious makes me wonder
if I even deserve it.
Thank you.
All right, now we'll taste the dish
from Private First Class
Kang Seong-jae of Ganglim Outpost.
After tasting something so incredible
this one looks quite plain in comparison.
Yes.
I'm not sure you can even
call this a "special meal."
It is a special meal.
But it just looks like
a typical home-cooked meal.
For sure.
He's not in the same league
as the guys from the Officers' Mess.
I suggest you eat it as you do at home.
Put some kimchi on a spoonful of rice
and then wrap it in the seaweed.
- Mom.
- My In-tae's favorite side dish.
Eat up.
- What?
- Is he crying?
Our heartless Division Commander
- is actually crying.
- Is there something wrong with him?
- He's crying.
- Is it that good?
- Mom.
Just one more. Eat one more before you go.
My son, you're having a hard time,
aren't you?
Come on, let's eat.
- Mom.
- Sir.
- What?
Gosh, I made a fool of myself by crying.
At first glance
I thought this was
just another home-cooked meal.
But the more I ate
the more it tugged at my heartstrings.
Where did you learn to cook this dish?
I didn't learn it from anywhere, sir.
I pictured my cozy home,
a place that's always been my sanctuary
and relied completely
on my senses to create it.
For many soldiers
including myself, what we miss the most
during our military service
is a home-cooked meal.
We may be dependable and strong soldiers
but a part of our hearts
always longs for our families.
I believe
that the warmth
of a single home-cooked meal
has the power to soothe that longing.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- Salute!
- Perfect! This is delicious!
All right,
the judges' scores have been tallied.
We will now announce the final results.
Today
I made a meal I can be proud of,
even if I lose.
Thinking of my loved ones
through all the cuts from the knife
and burns on my hands
I created this meal with my own two hands.
And the final result is...
Congratulations. This year's winner is...
Ganglim Outpost!
Let's give another big round of applause
for our two hard-working soldiers!
Seong-jae did it!
Kang Seong-jae,
you really had me on pins and needles.
I never would have won without you two.
Thank you.
See? I knew you could do it.
Just watching them cook was pure torture.
My mouth was watering the whole time.
But it looks like you aren't too happy.
Even though your own guys
took first and second places.
I am happy, sir.
Now let's hear a few words
from our winning team.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae!
First of all, the Outpost Commander
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun,
and Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol.
Without their help,
I never would have been able to win.
Today, as the cook for Ganglim Outpost
I wanted to do one last thing for them.
Wait.
What do you mean, your "last thing"
as the cook for Ganglim Outpost?
Is something going on at Ganglim?
About that, sir.
The battalion commander mentioned
that there were safety concerns
being raised about Ganglim
so we were in the process
of shutting it down.
If there are safety issues,
then shutting it down is the right call.
The safety of our soldiers
is our top priority, after all.
May I have a word, sir?
- Salute!
- Salute.
I came because I have something
I must report to you, Division Commander.
- And you are...
- The 4th Company Commander
Captain Hwang Seok-ho, sir.
What is it you wish to say?
In fact, our Ganglim Outpost
is safer than any other outpost.
What are you talking about?
This is the safety report
for Ganglim Outpost.
This report, under orders
from the battalion commander
was intentionally fabricated
to make the outpost appear unsafe.
What are you talking about?
Are you saying they intentionally tried
to shut down the outpost?
Division Commander,
it's a misunderstanding.
In order to silence the soldiers
at Ganglim Outpost
who spoke out about the food supplier
and with the ulterior motive
of having them disbanded
the closure procedure was initiated.
Then...
- there's just one favor I need to ask.
- Yes, sir. Please tell me.
I'm thinking this might be
a good chance to clean up Ganglim.
Submit a few reports up the chain
that there are concerns about accidents
due to the outpost's deterioration.
BUSINESS CLOSURE FORM
Again, I apologize
for causing you concern.
Salute!
I'm going to look
more into those documents
I saw in the Battalion Commander's office.
Then...
What can I do to help?
While Lieutenant Colonel Baek Chun-ik
is at the cooking competition
I need you to help me find the evidence.
My goodness, I just knew it.
They just changed the company name
and signed a new contract
over and over again.
He's been pulling this the whole time.
I never took the Battalion Commander
for that kind of man.
It was right under my nose.
Hey, Investigator.
Take all of this too. Wait a minute.
Let me just take a picture
before you take these.
Yes, thank you for your work.
You can take them.
If this isn't defense industry corruption,
what is?
This is why we were always
getting rotten eggs and stuff, right?
You can't blame Yoon Dong-hyun
for his cooking
when he could only use
ingredients like that.
Kang Seong-jae is the one
who deserves credit for his good work.
When a problem arose,
they'd terminate the contract
and have the business shut down.
But in reality, they were contracting
with the same company
- under a different name.
- Hey, Hwang Seok-ho!
Do you have any idea where you are,
talking so recklessly?
- Company Commander, continue.
- Furthermore
Major Im Seung-bin, who died a year ago
during a corruption investigation,
was also wrongly framed.
I have confirmed it.
What is it?
How are you holding up?
How do you think I'm holding up?
Has the Battalion Commander come to visit?
Everyone is too busy cutting ties with me.
Did the Battalion Commander
promise you my position?
A position... Is that really so important?
Is that why you went so far? To Major Im?
- What are you talking about?
- He was so good to us.
So, what exactly
did you come here to hear?
You didn't do this alone, did you?
I will handle it properly.
Min-gu.
You get what I'm saying, right?
I...
used to love how you were
like a cornered rat
that would even bite the cat.
But you don't have that fire
in you anymore.
I don't want to be disappointed again.
Major Lee Min-gu.
I suppose if it's a matter
of responsibility
then it's mine for failing
to manage my subordinate.
But if I had known about this beforehand
I would've stopped it one way or another.
Min-gu.
I didn't know it would go that far.
I was just following
the Battalion Commander's orders.
I would've been finished otherwise.
What choice did I have?
He told me to send the money, so I did.
Let's talk about this outside.
The Deputy Battalion Commander,
Major Im Seung-bin
found out about the kickbacks
from the supplier.
Hey, you scumbag.
So you framed him for everything
and drove him to his death.
Was that on your direct orders,
Battalion Commander?
Let's take this outside.
I think we need an explanation,
Battalion Commander.
Hey, you idiot.
What do you think you're doing? Darn it.
Excuse me for a moment.
Salute!
Master Sergeant Park Jae-young,
Administration and Supply NCO
for the 4th Company,
1st Battalion, 60th Regiment.
I'm here on business
regarding the cooking competition.
Salute!
Lieutenant Colonel Baek Chun-ik.
We've managed to secure all the evidence.
I'm sorry
but I don't think
you'll be able to get out of this.
- Investigators, please go ahead.
- Yes.
Don't touch me. Darn it.
What are you doing? Drag him out.
I will return
after I have explained my position!
Salute!
29TH DIVISION COOKING COMPETITION
- Company Commander.
- Company Commander!
Oh my. What a mess.
You went through a lot.
Geez, talk about timing.
If I'd been just a little later,
it would've been a huge disaster.
I was worried the competition
would be over by the time I arrived
but thanks to Private First Class Kang
making it to a rematch
- the timing was absolutely perfect.
- But hey, are you going to be okay?
This will probably affect your promotion,
Company Commander.
Well, what can you do?
I, Hwang Seok-ho, already did it.
But still
we can't let
any more injustices happen, right?
Right.
- You really went through it.
- Man, I'm beat.
Cho Ye-rin. You did a great job.
Not at all.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Congratulations.
- Thank you, sir.
- What are you congratulating him for?
Master Sergeant Park, we won.
First place? You're saying you won?
Oh my, Kang Seong-jae won. He won!
Oh my, hey, Kang Seong-jae actually won!
I learned a lot thanks to you,
Corporal Lee Ho-yeong.
I hope we can meet again.
Not at some small-time contest
like this one.
Let's have a proper showdown.
Chef to chef.
We'll see if that kind of home cooking
works then, too.
- Look at him.
- Geez, showing off until the end.
Man, he's got some great pride.
I wonder if you just kicked
the hornet's nest.
I think it'll be fun if we compete again.
Good. That's my guy.
Let's go.
Look at this.
Hero,
the Protect the Ganglim Outpost
quest is completed.
By winning the cooking competition
the Ganglim Outpost Shutdown
has been halted.
- Kang Seong-jae, come on.
- Let's go.
I'm coming.
Hey, you were really amazing today.
You really were.
You know what I was thinking
while I was crushing those biscuits?
"Once I'm done crushing these,
I get to go home."
But then suddenly, a tie! Then, a rematch!
I thought the world was out to get me.
Hey, Kang Seong-jae,
why were you just standing there
after the first round spacing out
like you'd lost your soul?
I thought he had a mental breakdown
and that I'd have to step in.
That would have been awful.
I think I was just really nervous.
The Division Commander
was there and everything.
Still, Kang Seong-jae
is definitely good under pressure.
What? But then...
- What is going to happen to our outpost?
- About that.
Since the Division Commander mentioned
that it was fine to leave Ganglim as is
don't you think we'll just go back
to our regular duties?
Gosh, Kang Seong-jae. On top of everything
you even saved an outpost
from being shut down?
Hey, you're really going
to make it big with your cooking.
- That's amazing.
GANGLIM OUTPOST
- You did great!
- Great job! Yes!
29TH DIVISION COOKING COMPETITION
1ST PLACE GOLDEN COOK AWARD
Hey, why is everyone out here in the cold?
We heard Kang Seong-jae won
and were waiting for you to get back.
Kang Seong-jae, if you were any later
everyone would've scattered
and started unpacking.
- I couldn't wait to see you all.
- What on earth did you cook
to stop the outpost from being shut down?
Hey! You take some hot rice
and pile on some back ribs and kimchi
and wrap it all up with seaweed
roasted in sesame oil...
- Talking makes my mouth water.
- Oh, right.
We only cooked it,
but we never got to try it.
- That's right.
- Yes!
Oh, right.
I'll prepare the meal right away!
Hey, this reminds me of that time
we went to pick namul.
I was so worried.
You all worked so hard.
Great job.
Gosh, this is delicious.
Eating this strangely puts me at ease.
It feels like I'm home.
We arrived at the battalion headquarters
and they suddenly told us to get on a bus.
We were told to return to the outpost.
So I wondered what was going on.
I instinctively knew
Kang Seong-jae had done something big.
You must have been really surprised today.
Kwan-cheol
Dong-hyun, and Seong-jae,
you all worked so hard.
- Yes, you did great.
- You did great!
This kitchen still needs me.
It breaks my heart to leave.
I just can't bring myself to leave.
Well, that's why I prepared
something special for you.
Is it pocket money?
It's an application
for Specialist Sergeant.
All right, everyone,
say hello to your new junior!
Our very own Staff Sergeant
Yoon Dong-hyun!
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun,
that's the first time I've seen that look.
That look on your face,
all serious and sweating buckets
while you were cooking...
What have you been doing all this time
to only show us that side of you now?
It's the last chapter
of my military life, isn't it?
I just thought it would be cool
to end it with a win.
It's no big deal.
Live a pure and clean life, like tofu!
Congrats on your discharge,
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun!
Anyone watching would think you're
getting out of prison, not the army.
He's being reborn, isn't he?
As a civilian.
Your sense of humor has really improved.
Dong-hyun, say a few words.
Did you just call his name?
- Jae-young!
- What?
- Ye-rin!
- Yes, go ahead. Say what you want.
You wanted to do this, right?
Man, really...
So, this is the end of my time
in the kitchen.
Kang Seong-jae.
Are you going to do this for me
when I get discharged too?
Hey, TMI, have some tact.
A Private First Class shouldn't be
talking about getting discharged.
Seong-jae, if Kwan-cheol gets cocky
when he makes Sergeant
just starve him. Got it?
All that knife work
was great mental training.
- Have a seat.
- Yes, sir.
Kang Seong-jae.
Thanks for all the good food.
It's all thanks to you,
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun. Thank you.
Oh, and there's one more thing!
One, two, three! Ta-da!
Hey, I can't eat something this cute.
It's adorable.
Hey, how'd you make this?
Gosh, he made rice inside an egg.
- Sergeant Yoon, are you crying?
- No, I'm not.
- Hey, are you crying?
- Don't cry!
- I'm not.
- Hey, this one's crying too!
- Why are you crying?
Oh, come on, sir.
Gosh, this is really moist.
Come on, let's eat.
Let's eat.
- Is that the new recruit?
- Yes, sir.
KANG SEONG-JAE
- Kang Seong-jae.
- Private Kang Seong-jae.
Here, use this.
Oh, thank you.
Hey...
Can't you just stay here?
- Grab my hand. Quick!
- Thank you.
Company, attention!
Salute Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun,
now a civilian!
- Salute!
- At ease.
- Is that the loudest you can be?
I can just imagine what a mess
the Ganglim Outpost
- will be without me.
- You should worry about yourself.
I don't care what you do out there,
but seriously, just don't cook.
But what can I do?
I've developed an interest in cooking.
If you get a job at a restaurant,
let us know where.
So we can make sure we never go there.
These punks are getting cocky
just because I'm a civilian now.
Attention.
You've all worked hard.
Just hang in there a little longer.
And...
I was truly grateful for everything.
- Especially you, Kang Seong-jae.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
You're really...
I can't figure you out.
Until the very end.
Thank you for your hard work, sir.
I'm heading out. It's cold.
You guys go on in. See ya.
- Take care, sir.
- Thank you for your hard work.
Hey, Dong-hyun.
- Take care.
- I'm off. Mun-ik, I'm really going.
- Go on, you old man!
KANG SEONG-JAE'S RECIPE NOTE
It feels like a dream.
Today, we're meeting someone
who, at the last cooking competition
took first place,
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Well, first, I was so grateful
that my fellow outpost soldiers
congratulated me, and most of all...
I'm just so glad I get to see
my fellow soldiers again.
Well, when people eat my food
I hope they feel like they've come home
and they can feel comfortable.
Filling the hearts of his comrades
with a single warm meal
this is Private First Class Kang Seong-jae
of the Ganglim Outpost.
This is Jeong Min-a,
reporting for Armed Forces TV.
GANGLIM OUTPOST
So how's work? You managing okay?
It's tough, but it's still fun.
I'm glad it seems to be
a good fit for you.
Oh, right.
I was so surprised when I saw you.
I knew you were a good cook
but I had no idea
you were that serious about it.
It was really impressive.
Thanks.
There's that pretty smile again.
Gosh, waiting for you
to get out of the army is taking forever.
What? Out of the blue?
This was always so hard for me.
I guess it's because
I wasn't sure of myself yet.
So you're more confident now?
But what if someone sees us?
"Certificate of Commendation.
Captain Hwang Seok-ho."
"This unit,
for its systematic unit management..."
Right?
"Something... So he is hereby
awarded this commendation."
"Division Commander,
Major General Kim In-tae."
Congratulations again, Company Commander.
If it weren't for all of you
I, Hwang Seok-ho,
couldn't have done anything.
And it's not just our Company Commander.
You all saw that our Ganglim Outpost
was selected as the best one, right?
What would've happened
if they'd shut down a post like this?
It would've been a huge mistake.
I know, right?
I'm so glad it all worked out.
You all went through so much trouble
because of me.
- Master Sergeant.
- Yes.
From now on,
go a little easier on the makgeolli
- and don't pick so many namul.
- There he goes again, nagging.
Well, our Company Commander
Hwang Seok-ho is back to his old self.
Ye-rin.
From now on, no matter what anyone says
keep being yourself
and always speak your mind.
Understood, Company Commander.
Hey, she'd do that
even if you didn't tell her to.
- Isn't that right?
- That's right.
All right, let's go eat.
- Where to? Outside?
- To the mess hall.
The mess hall? All right, let's go.
I wonder what delicious thing
Seong-jae has cooked up for us today. Huh?
Right.
Making rice at dawn every day
getting cut by knives,
and burning my hands
I slowly began to understand.
That a single meal I make
can give someone strength.
That its warmth can move a person's heart.
Making one meal
with all your heart every day.
That was the beginning of the legend.
Hero, a new quest has arrived.
The Legend Begins.
Become a cook who is recognized
in the Officers' Mess.
Do you wish to proceed?
SPECIAL THANKS TO LEE SANG-YI
THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
Private Kang Seong-jae.
DISLIKE LEVEL 40%
The Chef's Path tutorial has begun.
I'm truly grateful.
Start wearing this today.
Hey, you scoundrel!
Salute!
Warning.
I can't hear you!
- Salute!
Mamma mia!
Ganglim!
29TH DIVISION COOKING COMPETITION
Go, Ganglim!